wsistudents.com 2016-11-06

# Welcome to eWSI

Printable version | Back

PRIVACY POLICY

Franchise Support & Services, SLU (henceforth FSS) is committed to protecting your privacy. This "Privacy Policy" describes how we collect, store and use information on the individuals that use this website.

FSS complies with the legal requirements set out in the Spanish Personal Data Protection Act 15/1999, of December 13th (“Ley Orgánica de Protección de Datos Personales”). The term "personal data" as used in this Policy refers to information such as your name, e-mail address or mailing address, or any data that can be used to identify you. We ensure that our staff and those acting on our behalf obtain, use and disclose personal information lawfully and correctly.

In compliance with the Spanish Personal Data Protection Act (“Ley Orgánica de Protección de Datos Personales”), FSS informs you about the existence of an automated data file for which FSS assumes sole responsibility.

The purpose of the collection and processing of personal data from this website is twofold: to provide you with information on new services offered by this website; and to send you commercial information on products or services that may interest you. FSS will store these data as long as it is reasonably necessary to attain the mentioned purposes and in accordance with any applicable legal or ethical requirement.

By using this website, or providing information to us in other formats, you consent to the collection and use of this information by FSS. In addition, you are committed to supplying true, complete and accurate information and to keeping it up to date.

In order to use our services, users may be asked to fill in a form, which requires providing certain personal information to FSS. Unless otherwise provided in those fields expressly marked with an asterisk (*), answers to our questions on personal data are not mandatory. Not supplying the information required in such optional fields shall not represent any decrease of the services and information that we may provide you. However, failure to complete those compulsory fields or providing incorrect personal data shall prevent us from providing the requested information or services.

FSS informs you about the possibility of exercising your rights to access, amend, cancel and object to the processing of your personal data simply by making a written request to FRANCHISE SUPPORT & SERVICES, Tuset, 20-24, 5th Floor - 08006 Barcelona - Spain, Attention Privacy Controller or to our electronic mail address [privacy@wallstreetinstitute.com](mailto:privacy@wallstreetinstitute.com). Your requests will be dealt with in a prompt and proper manner.

FSS guarantees, in accordance with the terms set out in the Spanish Personal Data Protection Act (“Ley Orgánica de Protección de Datos Personales”), that your personal data will be treated in the strictest confidentiality, and that the server in which these data will be stored and dealt with has implemented the necessary industry-standard security measures to prevent accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access to the above-mentioned data.

We inform you that the sending of commercial communications containing information on services or products which may be of your interest will only be allowed in respect of users who have given their prior consent. Such consent may be revoked at any time, by making a written request to FRANCHISE SUPPORT & SERVICES, Tuset, 20-24, 5th Floor - 08006 Barcelona - Spain, Attention Privacy Controller or to our electronic mail address [privacy@wallstreetinstitute.com](mailto:privacy@wallstreetinstitute.com).

This website may use session cookies to track your progress while on the site. This website does not use “cookies” to collect information about you. A "cookie" is a small text file placed on your computer's hard drive or browser by a webpage server.

We do not send "spam". Spamming is defined as sending unsolicited e-mails, usually of a commercial nature, in large numbers and in a repeated manner, to individuals with whom the sender has had no previous contact or who have declined to receive such communications.

FSS logs IP addresses on the website, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for system administration and troubleshooting purposes. We occasionally use IP address logs to track distributive students and for the protection of other students. IP addresses are used to compile general traffic information. We will not attempt to identify individual users through their IP addresses.

This Privacy Policy applies only to this website, excluding third party websites. We may provide links to other websites, which we believe may be of interest to our visitors. We aim at ensuring that such websites are of the highest standard. However, due to the nature of the World Wide Web, we cannot guarantee the standards of every linked website or be responsible for their content.

If we amend our Privacy Policy in order to adapt it to new legal requirements, we will immediately post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we gather, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you have any queries or comments on this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the following e-mail address:[privacy@wallstreetinstitute.com](mailto:privacy@wallstreetinstitute.com).

Printable version | Back
